tech-pro.net 2016-10-31

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy explains how information is handled when you visit this site, and when you purchase products or services using links from this site.

### Personal information

Tech-Pro.net values your privacy. We do not retain personal information about visitors to this site. The only information this site may request from you is your name and email address. You will only be asked for this information if:

  * you purchase a Tech-Pro branded product.
  * you send us an email or open a support ticket.

We hate spam as much as you do. Tech-Pro.net **guarantees** that we will not use any information received from this website for any purpose other than that for which you provided it.

### Cookies and other tracking technologies

Most websites use cookies - small data files that are stored temporarily by your browser - to add functionality, improve your browsing experience and enable the operation of certain features. Cookies are a necessary part of the operation of most modern websites. For example, they may be used to store the details of items purchased on a website so that the items can be displayed when you reach the shopping cart page.

**Tech-Pro.net does not use cookies.** However, third party sites linked from this site may place cookies on your computer, for example to record that you reached the site via a link from Tech-Pro.net. The information stored in these cookies is not personally identifiable, and simply enables third party sites to compensate Tech-Pro.net for its role in referring visitors to the site.

Tech-Pro.net uses third-party advertising companies, primarily Google, to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may store non personally identifiable information in cookies in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. For more information about the DoubleClick cookie used by Google see the [DoubleClick privacy policy](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx). To discover how to opt out of receiving DoubleClick cookies, [click here](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html).

### Web server logs

In common with almost all websites, the web server on which this site is hosted logs non personally identifiable information related to visitors' use of the website. Tech-Pro.net may analyze the information collected by the web server for trends and statistics, or we may employ third party analysis services to collect and analyze site usage information for us, in order to improve the effectiveness of the site.

### E-commerce

Electronic commerce (e-commerce) transactions made through this site are made using third party payment processing services such as [Plimus](http://www.plimus.com/), [RegNow](http://www.regnow.com/), [ShareIt](http://www.shareit.com/) or [eSellerate](http://www.esellerate.net/), which work on behalf of the developer of the product you purchase. Tech-Pro.net is not involved in the transaction and never receives your credit card details or other personal or financial information.

Your legal contract of sale is with the company that processed your payment. In the event of a dispute (such as non-receipt of a product or license key) you are advised first of all to contact the product developer who has a contractual obligation to the payment processing company to fulfil the order.

Third party payment processing sites have their own privacy policies. Please consult them if you require more information.
